(Faceless female corpse - part 1)
Trying on earrings?
Just looking.
Take them off. They don't suit you.
Really? Are they that bad?
Yes! Look at your baby fat!
These are too lady-like for you.
You're hateful, Emma Hong!
That hurts, Elsa Hong!
Serve you right for calling me fat.
I wouldn't know how much you like them
if I didn't say that.
Get them if you like.
Look! They're expensive!
How much are they? My treat.
Are you serious?
Thanks, Sis!
Excuse me. Can you wrap this up?
Thank you, Miss Hong.
Next time we have new arrival from Italy,
I'll call you right away.
Thank you!
Wait!
Thanks!
Thank you.
You squander your money away.
Whenever Daddy pays us our allowance,
no wonder you spend it almost right away.
So what if we're out of cash?
We have this Hong Kong Pass.
It'll automatically top up.
Look at the time.
I better practice the piano,
or Mom and Daddy would give me grief.
How late can it be? Don't forget,
they're going to the hospital's
charity party tonight.
They won't be home soon.
Piano? What is it? Something you can eat?
Thank you.
Thanks.
Here's your change and receipt.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Bye! Come again.
Sis, I'm still worried.
Not while I'm here. Come on.
Is that your phone?
Hello? Yes...tonight.
OK! Bye!
Why do you have two phones?
How hard is that? Don't fuss.
Don't tell Mom and Daddy either.
Especially Daddy, OK?
Don't worry! I took your hush money.
Dr. Hong, the operation went well?
Very well.
Here's your report.
Good. Thanks.
This patient should have
their amniocentesis next week.
The diabetes report is out for this one.
Set up an appointment.
OK!
Dr. Hong, I finally get to see you.
Mr. Ho!
Yes, thanks for saving my wife and my son.
My wife can now breast feed.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
As long as they're both safe.
This is for you...
Please take it...
Thank you.
Thank you. I'll get out of your way.
Right!
Bye!
OK! About Mrs. Chan...
Mrs. Chan's appointment is tomorrow.
Dr. Hong, you overachieved today.
It's best to do it today.
Dr. Hong, your wife is in your office.
What time is it?
Almost 6 o'clock.
Really? I guess Mrs. Chan can wait.
Share the fruits with the others.
Thanks.
Thanks, Dr. Hong.
What's this pretty lady doing in my office?
What time is it, Doctor?
Looks like someone forgot the time again.
I knew it. That's why I came to pick you up.
The Director will tell you at the party,
you're the best doctor in the hospital.
But I'd rather be the best husband
in the world.
OK!
I'll go change. I won't be long.
Hey, hurry up!
Hey!
Long time no see!
I have been so busy.
Drink up...
Finish it...
Cheers...
Loser drinks.
Drink up...
You are bad. You come here often.
We're dead if Daddy found out.
I've seen enough of a bar.
Let's go home.
Hi, Lee!
What would you like?
The usual for me.
A Blue Hawaii for the pretty girl.
OK!
Thank you.
Don't be so boring.
We're OK if we get home before 10 o'clock.
You're either home or at the stupid library.
I need to show you more of this world.
Thank you.
Here you go...
Enjoy!
Cheers!
It's quite good.
See?
Hello? I'm here.
OK! Bye!
Who are you talking to?
Look at that smile! Boyfriend?
Don't be nosy! I'm not telling you.
You said sisters should have no secrets.
Come on, tell me!
You want to know?
OK, finish this and I'll tell you.
Hi, Ken!
Hey!
I'll be right back.
Drain the glass before I get back.
Cheers...
Hey!
She has an open mind.
I got something for you.
Thanks.
What is that?
Police! Hit the lights and kill the music.
Who's in charge?
Please cooperate. Get your ID cards ready.
Follow me!
What now?
Climb down!
Go!
It's so high!
We're dead if you don't.
Police! Open the door!
Anyone in there?
Anyone?
Elsa, grab my bag!
Anyone inside? Open the door!
Get the key!
Answer me! Anyone inside?
I got something for you.
That good?
Open up!
Madam, the key!
Thanks.
Check the toilets.
Right!
Watch out!
Come back...
You're home! Everything OK?
Are you OK?
Listen up, both of you!
You're grounded for a week.
Felix, don't do this.
Don't defend them.
How many times did I tell them?
Stay away from places with
undesirable characters.
You know bars are off limits.
They just don't listen.
Hong Ka-lam, don't take that attitude
with me!
Stop!
Hong Ka-lam, stay right there.
What attitude is this?
See?
How many times have you been to a bar?
When did you set a tracker on my phone?
That's outrageous!
You're outrageous!
I let you go the first couple of times.
But you keep going back.
This time, you even brought your sister.
You want to get the family in trouble?
I wasn't getting anyone in trouble.
I'm old enough to be in a bar.
What's the problem?
No problem?
It's clearly stated in the house rules.
No bars!
Bars have undesirable characters
who will attract the Police.
You almost got busted today
because you don't have an ID.
If you got busted,
you'll bring the cops to our front door.
Your Mom...overstayed her visa.
She'll get busted too. Then what?
Are you worried about Mom getting busted?
Or you don't want to go to jail?
You broke the law from the start.
You didn't want to go to jail.
Why must Elsa and I be punished for it?
All my life, I'm cooped up in my room.
It's a jail sentence.
Don't you think you're being selfish?
Who's being selfish now?
You don't like going to jail?
I'll put you in jail.
I'll lock you in your room for a week. Move!
I'm not going. Let go...
Come on...
No!
Move it...
I'm not going. You do this every time.
No one ever has any say.
You're a selfish, control freak.
Shut up!
Get in...
If you won't admit your mistake
after a week,
you'll be locked up until you do.
Let me out! You have no right to lock me up!
You self-centered, control freak!
Let me out!
Felix, don't do this.
The punishment is too harsh.
Don't try to defend her.
Listen, other than food,
don't open the door for any reason.
Don't let her out.
What happened to your hand? Let me see...
Just a small cut...
Small cut? Look at the wound!
Mia, take her to my study.
I'll be with you after I lock
the balcony door. Go!
Don't worry, it'll sting a bit.
You think Daddy is overbearing and despotic?
All your life, whatever you want to learn,
wherever you want to go,
I never stopped you.
You always got what you wanted.
I only want you to follow some simple rules
so you won't blow your cover.
Is it really that hard?
You're beginning to misbehave
and you're picking up your sister's
bad habits.
And you went to a dangerous place today.
Well? Does it still hurt?
Maybe not you. But your Mom is hurting.
Sorry, Mom!
Daddy did this for your own good.
Daddy, I'm in on it as well.
Don't blame everything on Emma.
I wanted to know what a bar looks like.
That's why she took me there.
If you want to go, you should have told me.
You're old enough to know
places where you should and should not go.
OK, get up.
Stay off spicy or deep-fried food,
shrimps and crabs.
Your Mom should know.
You think I'm ferocious?
I shouldn't lock up your sister?
You feel bad about this?
Anything you wish to say to me? Or ask me?
I have always wanted to ask one thing.
Why can't Emma and I have an ID card?
Did you and Mom get married overseas?
Twenty years ago,
Mom and Daddy met in a private member club.
I was a singer then.
(Wise men say only fools rush in)
(but I can't help falling in love with you)
(Like a river flows surely to sea)
(Darling, so it goes)
(some things are meant to be)
(Take my hand)
(Take my whole life too)
(for I can't help falling in love with you)
Police! Who's in charge?
Sir! Madam! What is it? I'm the manager.
We're looking for illegal workers.
What illegal workers?
Summon your staff
and ask them to get their ID cards ready.
Mia?
Sorry! Why do you look so scared?
Is something wrong?
No.
Some of your colleagues
were arrested for not having a working visa.
You don't have one either?
You saw through me.
Looks like I won't get away this time.
I'm a doctor.
A doctor won't arrest anyone.
A doctor? That's an honest profession.
You must look down on
illegal workers like me.
Why would I?
I think everyone must have a reason
for doing what they did.
I don't think you wanted this to happen.
You must have ineffable reasons, right?
Actually, when I came to Hong Kong,
I was happy to find a good job.
But my boss ran away.
Luckily, a friend found me
this part-time job.
I needed to stay longer to make more money.
Now I have overstayed.
You're so pretty and such a good singer,
I'm sure someone will hire you
for a permanent job.
Madam, please give me a chance.
Police!
I only wanted to make money.
I have two kids to support.
Why is it we're like in the movies?
I wonder how this plot will end.
What is it? You're not feeling well?
Sorry!
Well?
Oh dear, a life is at stake.
I'm just kidding. I'm thrilled.
We're going to be parents.
But we can't get married.
Even if we don't register to get married,
we can still have children.
Our home is big enough for us.
The whole family can live here.
But I can't go to the hospital.
How can I have the baby?
Have you forgotten I'm a doctor?
I can deliver a dozen babies for you.
Without a birth certificate,
the baby won't have an ID card.
We can live without an ID card.
I'll do my best to protect you.
The question is are you willing
to spend the rest of your life with me
and build a family.
I personally delivered you both.
I dare say I love you
as much as any other father.
To protect you,
that's why I set the rules for you.
After all these years,
we're doing rather well.
That means our rules worked.
I know, unlike other kids
you and your sister can't go to school.
So we taught you at home.
Any extra-curricular activities you like,
I will try my best to let you learn.
Let's see...
When you're sick, I make you well
and look after you.
Bye...
Thanks.
I gave your Mom a supplementary card
and I gave you and your sister cash
and this Hong Kong Pass to make purchases
that does not require an ID card.
So far, no one has doubted you.
That's brilliant. You can make
your own purchase.
There's still something I don't understand.
If Mom admits to the Government
she's an overstayer,
she'll be sent back to her place of origin
and then apply to come to Hong Kong again.
Emma and I can get our ID cards.
We won't have to do this.
Right, Mom?
Elsa, everyone has a reason for doing
what they did.
If Mom doesn't want to talk about it,
she must have a reason.
I hope you can understand, OK?
Help! Anyone out there?
I can't open the door!
Elsa, don't be scared.
Let me think of something.
Elsa...I'm here!
Sis...
Elsa, don't be scared.
Before Mom and Daddy come home,
I'll stay with you.
If Mom and Daddy saw me visiting you,
you'll get thrown in jail too.
You should hurry back.
Don't worry! Daddy gave me seven days.
I can leave the room, I just can't go out.
Even if Daddy knew I visited you,
he'll just extend my sentence.
I'm staying here with you tonight.
Once upon a time, there were
two little pigs.
A fat one and a thin one.
Then the big bad wolf shows up.
Guess which one he'll eat first?
The fat one.
If you were not in this house,
I'd really go crazy.
Actually, Daddy has a point.
How could you take his side?
Daddy lets us go everywhere we want.
He just didn't want us to go somewhere
the Police is likely to check our ID cards.
Hong Ka-yee, you have been brainwashed
like in a cult.
Let's not talk about this.
Remember I tossed my backpack in a fit?
Did Daddy go through my things?
Worried about your secret phone?
Relax! I hid it.
You're brilliant!
You bet.
When did he put a tracker in my phone?
Luckily, this morning
I reset a super long password.
He won't be able to unlock my phone again.
You should talk.
You didn't tell me about your secret phone
and about your boyfriend.
I have people I want to meet
and things I want to do.
Never mind...you won't understand.
Why not? I saw at the bar
you were quite chummy with that guy.
Is he your boyfriend?
You defied Daddy because of the dude?
Where are you going? Answer me!
A "dude"? That's rather vulgar.
Don't let Daddy hear you.
Or he'll say I'm a bad influence
and give me a longer sentence.
I don't live in a cave.
I go online and watch TV.
I pick up a few terms, what's the big deal?
Don't change the subject.
Is he your boyfriend?
You're such a nosy parker!
You're such a genius.
You played dumb in front of Mom and Daddy.
Look how sneaky you are now.
Nothing compared to you.
I've been asking you a question,
you still haven't answered me.
I don't want you to tell on me.
Am I a snitch?
If Daddy were to extort a confession
with torture,
you'll spill the beans on me.
Torture? That's crazy!
Oh my...you're calling me crazy?
You're ready to spread your wings?
Yes, I'm ready to fly.
(A week later)
I just finished my spa.
I'm coming over to you now.
But I have so much to read...
Hi, Elsa!
Hi, YY!
I saw you over there just now.
Why did you move?
The air con is too cold.
I came looking for you.
Here...
The Sane Cat concert?
The tickets are hard to get!
A friend of a friend got them...for Sunday.
You said you like this band.
I want to know if...
Why? You're busy that day?
You want to sell them?
No...I'm not busy.
I want to ask you to go with me.
This Sunday?
Yes, are you busy?
I can't.
Something I need to do at home. Sorry!
But didn't you want to see them live?
Why don't you ask your family...
Sorry! I need to run.
Let's go, Mom!
Who's that guy?
Someone I ran into a few times
at the library.
Just a quick chat.
You shouldn't be talking to strangers.
Daddy is worried about you
meeting undesirable characters.
Stay away from strangers.
I'm coming back...
Sorry! I'll talk to you later.
Sorry, I broke it.
It's OK. It's quite old.
No, I broke it.
But I don't have cash.
Do you have any electronic account
so I can transfer the money?
I don't. It's OK. No need to pay me.
No, I broke it.
How about...I buy you a new one.
Next time I see you at the library.
I'll give it to you.
OK. Thanks.
Can you give me your phone number?
Phone number?
Don't get me wrong...
This is not an excuse to get your number.
I wanted to let you choose the color
when I shop for it.
OK!
You're Elsa? I'm YY.
Hi!
This model is in black or white.
What color would you like?
Black, please. Thanks.
You're welcome.
I seem to see you at the library a lot.
Are you in school or working?
I'm in school.
Which one?
HKIU, Hong Kong Island University.
It's my gap year.
That's where I graduated.
Have you tried the dorm canteen?
Is the food still as bad?
Can't believe I picked his alma mater.
Better shut up before I give myself away.
Sorry, I have another call.
Talk to you later.
OK! Later...
Notes from the Underground?
Hi!
Hello!
Here...
Thanks.
You bought the upgraded version?
It's expensive. Let me pay you back.
No need. I promised to pay for it.
Thanks.
Can I ask you a question?
I notice you love to read,
but I have not seen you borrow a book.
Really? I see you in the library too.
But I seldom see you read any books.
What are you doing here?
I'm a reporter. I'm here to do research.
You probably didn't notice me.
I need to get to work.
Right!
The world is not full of baddies.
What?
Nothing. Where are we going?
Let's go buy something to eat
to cheer your sister up, OK?
Two fruit tarts, please?
Sure! What kind would you like?
Raspberry and mango.
No problem. Just a moment.
Right!
Your sister loves fruit tarts.
This should cheer her up.
She's been locked up for ten days.
That should make anyone crazy.
No food would help.
When I brought her breakfast,
she looks peaky.
I asked her who she met at the bar.
But she wouldn't tell me.
When you went with her last time,
did you meet her friends?
I don't know. It was my first time.
The Police came soon after we arrived.
I asked her when we came home
but she wouldn't tell me.
She wasn't like that before.
She never went drinking.
She must have met someone
who's a bad influence.
Decent people go to bars as well.
The world is not full of baddies.
You should know that, Mom.
What are you talking about?
You met Daddy at a club.
What do you know, kid?
Your fruit tarts are ready.
Great! Thanks.
Thank you.
Hello, Director? The delivery room
has several emergency surgeries.
Can you call Dr. Hong?
You can forget it.
Dr. Hong is busy at home
and took two weeks off.
I'll call other hospitals for you.
This is madness...
Don't think you have won.
Because you haven't.
I won't listen to you anymore.
He's playing the hi-fi?
Just because your music is blaring,
I can still make a lot of noise.
He cut the power? That's so childish!
You think cutting the power will shut me up?
No way. I can make noise with other things.
(So Ti La Ti La So)
What's going on?
Let's go look upstairs.
(Do Re Mi Fa So La So)
(So La Ti)
(Do Re Mi Do)
Enough of your madness!
Yes, I have gone mad!
You made me mad...
(Do Re)
Felix, stop it!
Just ignore her. Go back downstairs...
(So Ti La Ti La So)
(Do, Do Re Mi Fa So La)
(Three weeks later)
Emma...she's eating less and less.
Mom, why don't you talk to Daddy.
See if he'll let her out sooner.
I'm worried she can't take this much longer.
Felix, this has gone on for a month.
Is it time to let Emma out?
Daddy, I'm sure Emma learnt her lesson.
Please let her out.
You think this is the attitude of
someone who learnt her lesson?
I need her to understand
the family will always come first.
At least let her out for a breather.
Don't cave in.
Emma is sneaky.
No matter what she says, do not let her out.
Aren't you going to the market?
I'll drop you.
OK!
Emma, I'm going to get groceries.
I'll make you lasagna later, OK?
Emma?
Never mind her. Let's go.
OK!
Watch your sister for me.
Emma, it's me.
Mom and Daddy went out.
Answer me, OK? I'm worried about you.
Emma!
Emma, what's wrong?
My stomach hurts.
You had a relapse?
Maybe. I ran out of meds.
What should I do?
Get some from Daddy's study.
Can you get me some?
Right...hang in there. I'll be right back.
Emma, I got your meds.
Hang in there!
I'll pry this open...
I got your meds. Hurry...
Brilliant! I'm free!
I thought you were sick.
Why are you dressed like that?
What are you doing?
Need you ask? Isn't this obvious?
You're running away?
Don't! If Mom and Daddy found out,
they'll kill me. Don't go!
You don't understand. I must do this.
Daddy is unreasonable.
I can't let him lock me up forever.
If I don't run away, I'll never be free.
Just think, I'd be miserable if I stayed.
You don't want me to be miserable, right?
Where did you hide my backpack?
In my room.
Brilliant! You knew to hide it.
Here...
Thank you.
Daddy took my old phone.
Do you know where it is?
I don't.
Maybe in the safe?
You know the combination?
Where's the phone?
Forget it!
He put a lot of money inside.
He put in money every month
so he can give us the allowance.
I saw the combination one time.
Where is my phone?
Look again.
Forget it. I still have this one.
Wait! Are you sure about this?
I'm positive.
If Daddy should ask you,
just tell him I feigned an illness
to con you into opening the door.
Tell him I'm only borrowing the money.
I'll pay him back as soon as I can.
If you took the money,
God knows what Daddy will do
when he's pissed.
Don't worry. Daddy loves you,
he won't do anything to you.
But you'll earn a good scolding
because of me.
Sorry! Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone about the family.
I will protect you and Mom
and won't get you in trouble.
Dr. Hong!
Yes?
While you were in surgery
your wife called about an emergency.
OK, thank you.
Hello, Mia? What's so urgent?
Don't blame Elsa.
She was worried about Emma,
that's why she opened the door.
I can't believe she'd run away
and took $1M with her.
Why does she need so much money?
You two are close,
you must know where she is.
I really don't.
She just said it was a loan.
She'll pay it back later.
She promised she'll keep our family secret
and won't get us in trouble.
What happened to her?
We were doing so well as a family.
Why must she destroy everything?
I already told you the girls are grown up,
locking them inside the house won't work.
What should we do about Emma?
She's running around with so much cash.
And God knows who she's hanging out with.
She can't go far without an ID card.
I better go find her.
I'll go with you.
(Later that night)
What's the password?
Now it's locked.
We looked all night but couldn't find her.
We dared not ask around and catch
people's attention.
They may call the Police.
What should we do now?
It's dangerous for her to be
out there alone.
I know.
But we've been to places she
usually goes to.
It's late. She must have found
a place to stay.
(Next day after Emma left)
I'll always tell you where I am.
You did not.
(Day 4 after Emma left)
Daddy...
Elsa!
You were home late last night?
Mom and I looked for Emma all night.
Mom just went to bed.
(Day 7 after Emma left)
Happy birthday to you...
Happy birthday to Daddy...
Happy birthday to Felix...
Happy birthday to you.
I already told you the girls are grown up,
locking them inside the house won't work.
I'll lock you in your room for a week. Move!
I'm not going. Let go...
Come on...
No! You're a selfish, control freak.
Shut up!
If you won't admit your mistake
after a week,
you'll be locked up until you do.
Let me out...
When are you letting me out,
you control freak?
Let me out, you control freak.
You're self-centered...
Let me out, control freak...
You are a control freak!
What are you looking at?
I want to see what happened to you.
You did this to me.
You never treated me like a daughter,
or this house as your home.
No father would do this to his daughter.
You think you own the world
and everyone is your slave.
Who doesn't treat this place as a home?
Who's thinking only of herself
with no regard for any consequences
or the family?
Even if this is my home,
does that mean I can't go anywhere
or do anything for the rest of my life?
You have plenty of things to do
and places to go.
But no matter where you are
and what you're doing,
the family must come first.
You must learn to sacrifice yourself
for this family.
I won't listen to your crap anymore.
I knew you'd be rebellious.
That's why I took two weeks off
to watch you,
to ensure you understand
what I'm saying.
Go ahead! You think locking me up
means you have won?
You can lock me up, but not my mind.
Lock me up as long as you want,
but I'll never listen to you again,
control freak...
What is it?
What's wrong?
Look at this!
Female corpse found in the New Territories.
Bodies found by hikers is nothing new.
But this time the victim's face
was chewed up by wild boars
leaving behind a bloody mess.
It was a faceless corpse.
She has the same build as Emma.
It suits you. Get it.
Emma has the same top. It's Emma!